tomatocart.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy - TomatoCart

At TomatoCart we recognize the importance of your privacy and are committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is processed.

This Policy may be modified by us at any time when needed without notice to you. And we expect most changes will be minor. Please review it each time you visit TomatoCart or use any of our tools or services.

#### Information we collect and how we use it

We collect the following types of information:

  *  **Information you provide**

When you would like to post in our forum, we require you to register first. We ask you for personal information such as your name, username and email address. These collected registration information is available to TomatoCart forum members, the staff and volunteers.

When you purchase a product or service from us, we also request billing and shipping addresses, phone number, credit card number or other payment information. (Receipt information includes the name, address and phone number of the recipient, either yourself or someone else.) If a credit card number is collected it’s never stored on our servers. Such information is strictly confidential and only shared with shipping and payment processors, and/or selected partners as needed. This information is only used to complete the order.

We may update these data should you grant us permission to bill you or your credit card for recurring charges. All information of this nature is maintained by us in a secure database and transmitted across the Internet from you to us, using secured transmission encryption.

  *  **Cookies**

When you visit TomatoCart, we send to your computer one or more cookies, small programs that containing a string of characters. Cookies help analyze web traffic and tell the date and time when you access the website.

We employ these cookies in order to provide you with a better experience, including in storing your preference, improving search results, tracing visit trends, etc.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You may reset your browser in the HELP menu, to turn off the cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. But by refusing the cookies you may well reduce the enjoyment of the Internet.

  *  **Log information**

Our servers automatically keep a record of what your browser sends when you use TomatoCart services. These logs may include:

    * The IP address;
    * The type and language of browser and operation system you use to access the website;
    * The pages you visit;
    * The page address from which you followed a link to the website;
    * One or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

We use this information to help improve our website, to make it more useful to you.

  *  **User communications**

When you send an email or other communications to TomatoCart, we may retain those communications so as to reply to you and to improve our services. These addresses are used for no other purposes and are not shared with third parties.

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to polish up our site and to share with advertisers, such as the number of men forum members. We do not disclose anything that identifies you individually.

By visiting our website, you consent to the data collection in the way stated above.

#### Our commitment to data security

We do not, and will not allow third parties to track or collect your private information or associate gathered data with any private information from other sources. We prevent unauthorized data access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. We take appropriate physical, electronic and managerial measures to secure private information collected.

We will never reveal your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or we are requested by law to do so. If we propose to use personally identifiable information for other purposes not described in this document, we will offer you effective ways to opt out of the employment of your information for those other purposes. We will collect or use the information for those purposes only with your consent.

#### How you can access or update your information

We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that the data is needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We ensure that that data is accurate, complete, and current. We depend on you to update your personal information whenever necessary.

You can access your personally identifiable information that TomatoCart collects and maintains by logging in and clicking on “My Account” in the menu. We use it to better safeguard your information.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us [here](http://www.tomatocart.com/index.php/about-us/contact-us).

### Latest Blog Post

#### [TomatoCart v1.1.7 to v1.1.8 Upgrade Guide!](http://blog.tomatocart.com/?p=224 "Template Tutorial 1: Toys Store Theme")

The upgrade guide is a step-by-step tutorial to help users to upgrade TomatoCart v1.1.7 to v1.1.8. If you have not yet updated to v1.1.7, please review its upgrade guide before applying these changes. [...]

_By TomatoCart | august 21, 2012_
